saic.com 2019-07-03

# SAIC | Privacy Statement

At SAIC, we understand the concerns of users visiting www.saic.com ("Site"). SAIC respects your privacy and treats the information you provide us, including your Personal Information, with care. This Privacy Statement applies to our Site. It explains how we collect, use, and disclose information collected from you and the rights and choices available to you. View our Site's [Terms of Use](https://www.saic.com/terms-of-use).

This Privacy Statement does not apply to information collected from you offline, to SAIC websites not linked to this Privacy Statement or to third party websites linked to our Site. Your use of SAIC's websites which do link to this Privacy Statement is subject to this Privacy Statement and its related Terms of Use. Your use of third party websites is governed by their respective privacy policy.

### Personal and Other Information

Through your interaction and use of our Site, SAIC may collect "Personal Information", which is information that identifies or relates to an individual. As examples, Personal Information may include your name, physical address, telephone number, e-mail address, emergency contact details, company affiliation, and associated interests.

SAIC may also collect "Other Information" through your interaction with and use of the Site, which is not directly related to an individual. As examples, Other Information may include browser and device information, data collected through automated electronic interactions, application usage data, demographic information, geographic or geo-location information, and statistical or aggregated data.

Statistical or aggregated data does not directly identify a specify person, but it may be derived from Personal Information. For example, we may aggregate Personal Information to calculate the percentage of users in a particular zip code.

In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information. In such cases, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information.

### Information You Provide to Us

If you request or provide Personal Information through our Site using our online contact forms, we store the Personal Information you provide to assist us in responding to your requests.

If you apply for a job at SAIC, the Personal information we receive from you is used for employment consideration and other human resource purposes, such as communicating with you in writing, by telephone, or online; evaluating your application; analyzing our staffing needs and practices; or supporting other actions related to our hiring process and employee administration. We may combine your data with research tools and information from other sources. Unless you request otherwise, we may keep your Personal Information for future consideration. If you provide Personal Information through links to third party websites, you may be asked to provide additional information by these websites.

### Information We Collect by Automated Tools

When you access our Site, we may collect Other Information by automated means, including the use of cookies, web server logs, and third party analytics.

Cookies are small pieces of data or data files that are sent by a website to your web browser and stored on your computer. They are used to understand general traffic patterns on our Site. The Other Information stored in the cookie is used for statistical tracking and other purposes, but not for individual identification. Cookies are also used to prefill forms so that you do not need to re-enter the data, such as when you apply for a job online. We may use the aggregated data to provide feedback to our web designers, content providers, or business managers to assist them in improving our Site and services offered.

You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. If you select this setting, however, you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Site.

Additionally, our web servers may log Other Information such as your device type, operating system type, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located. We may also record Other Information such as the address of the webpage that referred you to our Site and the IP address of the device you use to connect to our Site. Additionally, we may log Other Information about your interaction with our Site, such as pages you visit.

We may also use third party web analytics to help us analyze how users engage with our Site. The Other Information collected will be disclosed to, or collected by, these third party service providers.

### How We Use Your Personal Information

In accordance with applicable laws, SAIC may use your Personal and Other Information for the purposes listed below:

  * to send you information you requested or "opted-in" to receive
  * to contact you in the event of an emergency
  * to evaluate your qualifications for employment and contact you, as appropriate, for employment opportunities
  * to support human resource functions including employee administration and analysis of hiring and recruitment processes
  * to submit bids for proposals and contracts from governmental or private entities
  * to identify, prevent, and protect against cybersecurity and other security events, espionage, fraud, unlawful activity, claims, and other liabilities
  * to comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements and standards consistent with industry practices and our policies

### Information We Share

Although SAIC does not sell, rent, or loan your Personal or Other Information to any third party, we may disclose such information as listed below:

  * if required by law or through a legal process
  * when we submit bids for proposals and contracts from governmental or private entities
  * when formally requested by law enforcement authorities or other government entities
  * when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent harm or financial loss
  * in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual espionage, cybersecurity or security events, or other fraudulent or illegal activity
  * any other legal purpose

We also may transfer Personal Information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business and assets.

### Online Recruiting Information

We may collect online recruiting information from individuals who visit our Site and are interested in pursuing job opportunities with SAIC. To this end, our Site may provide you with the opportunity to review and apply for available positions listed in an online jobs database and provide assistance to individuals needing a disability reasonable accommodation.

If you choose to proceed and gain access to this database through our Site, you will be linked to a third party website hosted and maintained by one or more of our service providers ("Online Recruiting Site"). The Online Recruiting Site will allow you to provide information (e.g., your CV, contact information and identification of SAIC positions of interest) that will be shared with SAIC and used to evaluate your eligibility for employment and contact you as appropriate. Please note that third party vendors may be responsible for operating the Online Recruiting Site, and their privacy practices may be different than SAIC's. We encourage you to review such privacy policies and terms of use posted on the Online Recruiting Site prior to submitting any Personal Information in connection with your employment application.

### Privacy of Children

SAIC does not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 on the Site, except as permitted by law. We do not knowingly allow children to communicate with us or use any of our online services. If you are a parent and become aware that your child has provided us with information, please contact us as provided below.

### How We Protect Personal Information

While SAIC is committed to protecting your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, we cannot fully eliminate all security risks. SAIC maintains safeguards to protect Personal Information, but no Internet system can be 100% secure.

### Changes to Privacy Statement

SAIC may modify this Privacy Statement at any time. We will notify users of changes by posting changes to the Site or by other appropriate means. We recommend you visit this page frequently to determine if any changes have occurred. You can determine when this Privacy Statement was last revised by referring to the "Effective Date" at the top of this page. Any changes to this Privacy Statement will become effective upon posting on this Site. A User’s continued use of the Site or provision of personal information to use the Site following such changes indicates acceptance to the revised Privacy Policy.

### Links to Other Websites

This Privacy Statement applies only to our Site. You should be aware that through links you may be directed to other websites that we do not control. SAIC has no control over the privacy notices, policies or practices of these other websites, and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites to which we link, list, rank or identify by means of a search. SAIC takes no responsibility for the products, services, policies, or actions of third parties or the content of third party websites. When you leave our Site and go to a third party website, we encourage you to read the privacy policies and other notices posted.

### Your Rights and Choices

At our Site, you can sign up to receive SAIC Email Alerts for information that interests you, such as the latest SAIC news and publications, as well as investor information including SEC filings, daily stock quotes, and more. We offer "opt-in" lists so you can sign up and sign off at any time. To unsubscribe, simply reply to the email address on the bottom of every email we send you.

### Your California Privacy Rights

California residents are entitled once a year, free of charge, to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of certain categories of personal data to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. [Insert designated contact point]. We do not share personal data with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

Do-Not-Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms. Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to the websites and other online services with which a user communicates. There is no industry standard that governs what, if anything, websites should do when they receive these signals. SAIC currently does not take action in response to these signals. If and when a standard is established and accepted, we will reassess how to respond to these signals.

### Consent to Data Transfer

While SAIC has active businesses in many countries around the globe, we are headquartered in the United States. Thus, if you proceed to use this site, your Personal Information may be transferred to or accessible by entities or individuals in the United States and processed according to the terms described in this Privacy Statement.

Personal Information collected by SAIC may be stored and processed in your region, in the United States, and/or in any other country where SAIC or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or service providers operate facilities. Typically, the primary storage location is in the United States or a customer’s region (which may also be the United States), often with a backup to a data center in a different region. Storage location(s) are chosen in order to operate efficiently, improve performance, and create redundancies to protect the data in the event of an outage or other problem.

We (or our service providers) may transfer Personal Information from the EEA to other countries, some of which have not yet been determined by the European Commission to have an adequate level of data protection. For example, those countries’ laws may not guarantee you the same rights, or there may not be a government authority capable of addressing your concerns. When we engage in such transfers, we use a variety of legal mechanisms, including contracts and written assurances from service providers, to help ensure your rights and protections travel with your Personal Information. To learn more about the European Commission’s decisions on the adequacy of the personal data protection in the countries where SAIC operates (such as the United States), please visit: [Adequacy of the protection of personal data in non-EU countries](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/adequacy-protection-personal-data-non-eu-countries_en).

By continuing to use this site, you authorize SAIC and its service providers to transfer your Personal Information to – or make it available in – destinations outside your home country and to process it according to this Privacy Statement. You may contact us at [L_privacy@saic.com](mailto:L_privacy@saic.com) for more information about the safeguards used protect your Personal Information if it is transferred outside of your country of residence.
